



ABOUT ME

5+ year experience in Front-End Development.
I have experience in developing sites of template and design type: landing page, corporate sites, online stores (WordPress + Woocommerce, Magento, Opencart) and individual projects (React)

Focus on Front-end tasks mostly using core JavaScript, JavaScript libraries, and modern frameworks (React, Vue)

OBJECTIVE: Work on exciting projects in a team with technologies (VUE.JS, REACT.JS).



CONTACT

+38 (063) 892-06-06
drobotun.nastia@gmail.com
linkedin/anastasiia-drobotun/



EDUCATION

National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Master's Degree

2015 - 2017

Information and communication systems security

National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Bachelor's Degree

2011 - 2015 Applied Mathematics

Anastasia Drobotun

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO SITE



WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

NDA Company, August 2022 - present

- Created and updated UI, bug-fixing, tasks estimation, markup;
- Development of modules, themes for Magento (M1, M2, Hyva);
- Installing a local environment with Docker;

Front-End Developer

SKYNIX, Desember 2019 - August 2022

- -Created new blocks on React from builder, create new components;
- -Created and updated UI, bug-fixing, optimization, tasks estimation, markup;
- -Development of modules, themes for Wordpress, Magento (M1, M2, Hyva);
- -Installing a local environment with Docker, XAMPP;

Front-End Developer

SEOWAVE, March 2018 - Desember 2019

- - Development of themes for CMS WordPress, OpenCart;
- - Creating template and design type websites: landing page, corporate websites, online stores, individual projects;



SKILLS | EXTRAS

- React, Vue, Redux, Next.js, TypeScript;
- Knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript;
- SASS/SCSS, LESS, TailwindCSS, BEM;
- Familiar with css-flex, grid, animation, SVG, PerfectPixel;
- Grunt, Webpack, Gulp;
- · Version control systems (Git);
- CMS (Wordpress, Opencart, Magento (M1, M2, Hyva);
- Knowledge of SQL, PHP;
- Photoshop, Zeplin, Figma, Adobe XD;
- English Pre-Intermediate;